我们刚刚编写的URIMatcher是我们编写
ContentProvider的核心
The URIMatcher we just coded is central
to coding our ContentProvider.
将会用于实现我们的ContentProvider方法中
And will be used in the implementation
of our core ContentProvider methods.
我们已经给你写好了测试来全程帮助你完成
WeatherProvider的编写
We've given you Tests to help you along
the way as you code WeatherProvider.
因为这里的部分测试用例也可以用在
Since several of these tests
have been re-purposed from
你之前帮助书写的数据库测试中
the database test you helped write.
你有可能想看看在任务中ContentProvider调用是如何替换
You may want to look at how the
ContentProvider calls replace the SQL
SQL数据库调用的，比如testLocationTable和testWeatherTable。
database calls in tasks such as test
location table and test weather table.
但是在我们开始实现第四步
测试我们的Content
But before we can start implementing
step four in testing our content
Provider时，我们需要将其注册到
AndroidManifest中，这样
provider, we need to register
it to the AndroidManifest, so
Android系统才知道它的存在。
that Android knows about it.
一旦WeatherProvider向
PackageManager注册，我们
Once the Weather Provider has been
registered with the package manager, we
可以使用一个名为ContentResolver的
Android工具类来获取它的引用
can use an Android utility class called
the ContentResolver to refer to it.
ContentResolver利用Content Authority
定位我们的类，然后
The ContentResolver locates our class
using the Content Authority and
直接为我们调用WeatherProvider
makes direct calls to the Weather
Provider on our behalf.
在androidmanifest.xml文件中加入一个
provider标签用于注册
Add a provider tag into
the androidmanifest.xml file to register
带Content Authority的
WeatherProvider类，就像
the WeatherProvider class with
the Content Authority as defined in
在WeatherContract中定义的。
the WeatherContract.
记住有两个领域你需要填充在provider标签内
Note that the two fields you need
to populate in the provider tag
是android:name和android:authority
are android:name and android:authority.
通常来说，在TestProvider内
的testProviderRegistry()
On common, the test provider
registry test within test provider
可以测试你是否正确完成了。
to test to see if you've
done this correctly.